{
  "Subject1": [
    {
      "Subject": "English",
      "English": [
        {
          "English": "1-3",
           "1-3" : [
             {
               "Diff": "Basic",
               "Basic" : [
                 {
                   "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
                   "Option1": "Apis",
                   "Option2":"Coleoptera",
                   "Option3":"Formicidae",
                   "Option4":"Rhopalocera",
                   "correctIndex": "Formicidae"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
                   "Option1":"1,233 K",
                   "Option2":"5,778 K",
                   "Option3":"12,130 K",
                   "Option4":"101,300 K",
                   "correctIndex": "1,233 K"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Who are the actors in The Internship?",
                   "Option1": "Ben Stiller, Jonah Hill",
                   "Option2": "Courteney Cox, Matt LeBlanc",
                   "Option3": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons",
                   "Option4": "Vince Vaughn, Owen Wilson",
                   "correctIndex": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the capital of Spain?",
                   "Option1": "Berlin",
                   "Option2": "Buenos Aires",
                   "Option3": "Madrid",
                   "Option4": "San Juan",
                   "correctIndex": "Buenos Aires"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                   "Option1": "Black, Red",
                   "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                   "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                   "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                   "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is 70 degrees Fahrenheit in Celsius?",
                   "Option1": "18.8889",
                   "Option2": "20",
                   "Option3": "21.1111",
                   "Option4": "158",
                   "correctIndex": "20"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "When was Mahatma Gandhi born?",
                   "Option1": "October 2, 1869",
                   "Option2": "December 15, 1872",
                   "Option3": "July 18, 1918",
                   "Option4": "January 15, 1929",
                   "correctIndex": "October 2, 1869"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "How far is the moon from Earth?",
                   "Option1": "7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
                   "Option2": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
                   "Option3": "238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
                   "Option4": "35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)",
                   "correctIndex": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is 65 times 52?",
                   "Option1": "117",
                   "Option2": "3120",
                   "Option3": "3380",
                   "Option4": "3520",
                   "correctIndex": "3120"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "How tall is Mount Everest?",
                   "Option1": "6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
                   "Option2": "7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
                   "Option3": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
                   "Option4": "29,029 ft (8,847 m)",
                   "correctIndex": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "When did The Avengers come out?",
                   "Option1": "May 2, 2008",
                   "Option2": "May 4, 2012",
                   "Option3": "May 3, 2013",
                   "Option4": "April 4, 2014",
                   "correctIndex": "May 2, 2008"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
                   "Option1": "0x18C1",
                   "Option2": "0xBEEF",
                   "Option3": "0xDEAD",
                   "Option4": "0x12D591",
                   "correctIndex": "0x18C1"
                 }
               ]
             },
             {
               "Diff": "Medium",
               "Medium": [
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of sentence?",
                   "Option1": "Declarative",
                   "Option2":"Interrogative",
                   "Option3":"Imperative",
                   "Option4":"Narrative",
                   "correctIndex": "Imperative"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is a synonym for 'diligent'?",
                   "Option1":"Lazy",
                   "Option2":"Hardworking",
                   "Option3":"Slow",
                   "Option4":"Unreliable",
                   "correctIndex": "Lazy"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the proper noun in the following sentence? 'The Eiffel Tower is in Paris.'",
                   "Option1": "The",
                   "Option2": "Eiffel",
                   "Option3": "Tower",
                   "Option4": "Paris",
                   "correctIndex": "The"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the past tense of the verb 'run'?",
                   "Option1": "Runned",
                   "Option2": "Runneded",
                   "Option3": "Ran",
                   "Option4": "Runneded",
                   "correctIndex": "Ran"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                   "Option1": "Black, Red",
                   "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                   "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                   "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                   "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is a compound word?",
                   "Option1": "Bird",
                   "Option2": "House",
                   "Option3": "Basketball",
                   "Option4": "Table",
                   "correctIndex": "House"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the correct verb tense to use in the following sentence? 'I _____ my homework yesterday.'",
                   "Option1": "Do",
                   "Option2": "Did",
                   "Option3": "Done",
                   "Option4": "Doing",
                   "correctIndex": "Do"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                   "Option1": "Childs",
                   "Option2": "Childen",
                   "Option3": "Children",
                   "Option4": "Childies",
                   "correctIndex": "Children"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                   "Option1": "And",
                   "Option2": "But",
                   "Option3": "Or",
                   "Option4": "Under",
                   "correctIndex": "Or"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                   "Option1": "She",
                   "Option2": "Sings",
                   "Option3": "Beautifully",
                   "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                   "correctIndex": "Sings"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                   "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                   "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                   "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                   "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                   "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                 }
               ]
             },
             {
               "Diff": "Hard",
               "Hard": [
                 {
                 "question": "Which of the following words means 'a fear of long words'?",
                 "Option1": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia",
                 "Option2":"Sesquipedalophobia",
                 "Option3":"Phobophobia",
                 "Option4":"Logophobia",
                 "correctIndex": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the correct possessive form of the name 'Jones'?",
                   "Option1":"Jones",
                   "Option2":"Jone's",
                   "Option3":"Jones's",
                   "Option4":"Joneses",
                   "correctIndex": "Jones's"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a rhetorical device?",
                   "Option1": "Metaphor",
                   "Option2": "Alliteration",
                   "Option3": "Onomatopoeia",
                   "Option4": "Synonym",
                   "correctIndex": "Synonym"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the difference between 'few' and 'a few'?",
                   "Option1": "There is no difference",
                   "Option2": "'Few' means none, while 'a few' means some",
                   "Option3": "'Few' means some, while 'a few' means many",
                   "Option4": "'Few' is an adverb, while 'a few' is a pronoun",
                   "correctIndex": "There is no difference"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'goose'?",
                   "Option1": "Gooses",
                   "Option2": "Goosen",
                   "Option3": "Geese",
                   "Option4": "Gooseses",
                   "correctIndex": "Geese"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is a correlative conjunction?",
                   "Option1": "And",
                   "Option2": "But",
                   "Option3": "Or",
                   "Option4": "Neither...nor",
                   "correctIndex": "Neither...nor"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is an example of an indirect object?",
                   "Option1": "He gave her a book.",
                   "Option2": "She ran quickly to the store.",
                   "Option3": "The sun set behind the mountains",
                   "Option4": "I ate pizza for dinner.",
                   "correctIndex": "He gave her a book."
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                   "Option1": "Childs",
                   "Option2": "Childen",
                   "Option3": "Children",
                   "Option4": "Childies",
                   "correctIndex": "Children"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                   "Option1": "And",
                   "Option2": "But",
                   "Option3": "Or",
                   "Option4": "Under",
                   "correctIndex": "Or"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                   "Option1": "She",
                   "Option2": "Sings",
                   "Option3": "Beautifully",
                   "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                   "correctIndex": "Sings"
                 },
                 {
                   "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                   "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                   "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                   "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                   "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                   "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                 }
               ]
             }
           ]
        },
        {  "English": "4-6",
          "4-6" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic",
              "Basic": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following words means 'a fear of long words (B 4-6)'?",
                  "Option1": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia",
                  "Option2":"Sesquipedalophobia",
                  "Option3":"Phobophobia",
                  "Option4":"Logophobia",
                  "correctIndex": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct possessive form of the name 'Jones'?",
                  "Option1":"Jones",
                  "Option2":"Jone's",
                  "Option3":"Jones's",
                  "Option4":"Joneses",
                  "correctIndex": "Jones's"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a rhetorical device?",
                  "Option1": "Metaphor",
                  "Option2": "Alliteration",
                  "Option3": "Onomatopoeia",
                  "Option4": "Synonym",
                  "correctIndex": "Synonym"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the difference between 'few' and 'a few'?",
                  "Option1": "There is no difference",
                  "Option2": "'Few' means none, while 'a few' means some",
                  "Option3": "'Few' means some, while 'a few' means many",
                  "Option4": "'Few' is an adverb, while 'a few' is a pronoun",
                  "correctIndex": "There is no difference"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'goose'?",
                  "Option1": "Gooses",
                  "Option2": "Goosen",
                  "Option3": "Geese",
                  "Option4": "Gooseses",
                  "correctIndex": "Geese"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a correlative conjunction?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Neither...nor",
                  "correctIndex": "Neither...nor"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of an indirect object?",
                  "Option1": "He gave her a book.",
                  "Option2": "She ran quickly to the store.",
                  "Option3": "The sun set behind the mountains",
                  "Option4": "I ate pizza for dinner.",
                  "correctIndex": "He gave her a book."
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium",
              "Medium" : [
                {
                  "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly? (M 4-6)",
                  "Option1": "Apis",
                  "Option2":"Coleoptera",
                  "Option3":"Formicidae",
                  "Option4":"Rhopalocera",
                  "correctIndex": "Formicidae"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
                  "Option1":"1,233 K",
                  "Option2":"5,778 K",
                  "Option3":"12,130 K",
                  "Option4":"101,300 K",
                  "correctIndex": "1,233 K"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Who are the actors in The Internship?",
                  "Option1": "Ben Stiller, Jonah Hill",
                  "Option2": "Courteney Cox, Matt LeBlanc",
                  "Option3": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons",
                  "Option4": "Vince Vaughn, Owen Wilson",
                  "correctIndex": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the capital of Spain?",
                  "Option1": "Berlin",
                  "Option2": "Buenos Aires",
                  "Option3": "Madrid",
                  "Option4": "San Juan",
                  "correctIndex": "Buenos Aires"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 70 degrees Fahrenheit in Celsius?",
                  "Option1": "18.8889",
                  "Option2": "20",
                  "Option3": "21.1111",
                  "Option4": "158",
                  "correctIndex": "20"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When was Mahatma Gandhi born?",
                  "Option1": "October 2, 1869",
                  "Option2": "December 15, 1872",
                  "Option3": "July 18, 1918",
                  "Option4": "January 15, 1929",
                  "correctIndex": "October 2, 1869"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How far is the moon from Earth?",
                  "Option1": "7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
                  "Option2": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
                  "Option3": "238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
                  "Option4": "35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)",
                  "correctIndex": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 65 times 52?",
                  "Option1": "117",
                  "Option2": "3120",
                  "Option3": "3380",
                  "Option4": "3520",
                  "correctIndex": "3120"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How tall is Mount Everest?",
                  "Option1": "6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
                  "Option2": "7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
                  "Option3": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
                  "Option4": "29,029 ft (8,847 m)",
                  "correctIndex": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When did The Avengers come out?",
                  "Option1": "May 2, 2008",
                  "Option2": "May 4, 2012",
                  "Option3": "May 3, 2013",
                  "Option4": "April 4, 2014",
                  "correctIndex": "May 2, 2008"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
                  "Option1": "0x18C1",
                  "Option2": "0xBEEF",
                  "Option3": "0xDEAD",
                  "Option4": "0x12D591",
                  "correctIndex": "0x18C1"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard",
              "Hard": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of sentence?(H 4-6)",
                  "Option1": "Declarative",
                  "Option2":"Interrogative",
                  "Option3":"Imperative",
                  "Option4":"Narrative",
                  "correctIndex": "Imperative"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a synonym for 'diligent'?",
                  "Option1":"Lazy",
                  "Option2":"Hardworking",
                  "Option3":"Slow",
                  "Option4":"Unreliable",
                  "correctIndex": "Lazy"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the proper noun in the following sentence? 'The Eiffel Tower is in Paris.'",
                  "Option1": "The",
                  "Option2": "Eiffel",
                  "Option3": "Tower",
                  "Option4": "Paris",
                  "correctIndex": "The"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the past tense of the verb 'run'?",
                  "Option1": "Runned",
                  "Option2": "Runneded",
                  "Option3": "Ran",
                  "Option4": "Runneded",
                  "correctIndex": "Ran"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a compound word?",
                  "Option1": "Bird",
                  "Option2": "House",
                  "Option3": "Basketball",
                  "Option4": "Table",
                  "correctIndex": "House"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct verb tense to use in the following sentence? 'I _____ my homework yesterday.'",
                  "Option1": "Do",
                  "Option2": "Did",
                  "Option3": "Done",
                  "Option4": "Doing",
                  "correctIndex": "Do"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]

            }
          ]
        },
        { "English": "7-9",
          "7-9" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic",
              "Basic": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following words means 'a fear of long words (B 7-9)'?",
                  "Option1": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia",
                  "Option2":"Sesquipedalophobia",
                  "Option3":"Phobophobia",
                  "Option4":"Logophobia",
                  "correctIndex": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct possessive form of the name 'Jones'?",
                  "Option1":"Jones",
                  "Option2":"Jone's",
                  "Option3":"Jones's",
                  "Option4":"Joneses",
                  "correctIndex": "Jones's"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a rhetorical device?",
                  "Option1": "Metaphor",
                  "Option2": "Alliteration",
                  "Option3": "Onomatopoeia",
                  "Option4": "Synonym",
                  "correctIndex": "Synonym"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the difference between 'few' and 'a few'?",
                  "Option1": "There is no difference",
                  "Option2": "'Few' means none, while 'a few' means some",
                  "Option3": "'Few' means some, while 'a few' means many",
                  "Option4": "'Few' is an adverb, while 'a few' is a pronoun",
                  "correctIndex": "There is no difference"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'goose'?",
                  "Option1": "Gooses",
                  "Option2": "Goosen",
                  "Option3": "Geese",
                  "Option4": "Gooseses",
                  "correctIndex": "Geese"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a correlative conjunction?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Neither...nor",
                  "correctIndex": "Neither...nor"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of an indirect object?",
                  "Option1": "He gave her a book.",
                  "Option2": "She ran quickly to the store.",
                  "Option3": "The sun set behind the mountains",
                  "Option4": "I ate pizza for dinner.",
                  "correctIndex": "He gave her a book."
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium",
              "Medium" : [
                {
                  "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly? (M 7-9)",
                  "Option1": "Apis",
                  "Option2":"Coleoptera",
                  "Option3":"Formicidae",
                  "Option4":"Rhopalocera",
                  "correctIndex": "Formicidae"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
                  "Option1":"1,233 K",
                  "Option2":"5,778 K",
                  "Option3":"12,130 K",
                  "Option4":"101,300 K",
                  "correctIndex": "1,233 K"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Who are the actors in The Internship?",
                  "Option1": "Ben Stiller, Jonah Hill",
                  "Option2": "Courteney Cox, Matt LeBlanc",
                  "Option3": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons",
                  "Option4": "Vince Vaughn, Owen Wilson",
                  "correctIndex": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the capital of Spain?",
                  "Option1": "Berlin",
                  "Option2": "Buenos Aires",
                  "Option3": "Madrid",
                  "Option4": "San Juan",
                  "correctIndex": "Buenos Aires"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 70 degrees Fahrenheit in Celsius?",
                  "Option1": "18.8889",
                  "Option2": "20",
                  "Option3": "21.1111",
                  "Option4": "158",
                  "correctIndex": "20"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When was Mahatma Gandhi born?",
                  "Option1": "October 2, 1869",
                  "Option2": "December 15, 1872",
                  "Option3": "July 18, 1918",
                  "Option4": "January 15, 1929",
                  "correctIndex": "October 2, 1869"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How far is the moon from Earth?",
                  "Option1": "7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
                  "Option2": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
                  "Option3": "238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
                  "Option4": "35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)",
                  "correctIndex": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 65 times 52?",
                  "Option1": "117",
                  "Option2": "3120",
                  "Option3": "3380",
                  "Option4": "3520",
                  "correctIndex": "3120"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How tall is Mount Everest?",
                  "Option1": "6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
                  "Option2": "7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
                  "Option3": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
                  "Option4": "29,029 ft (8,847 m)",
                  "correctIndex": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When did The Avengers come out?",
                  "Option1": "May 2, 2008",
                  "Option2": "May 4, 2012",
                  "Option3": "May 3, 2013",
                  "Option4": "April 4, 2014",
                  "correctIndex": "May 2, 2008"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
                  "Option1": "0x18C1",
                  "Option2": "0xBEEF",
                  "Option3": "0xDEAD",
                  "Option4": "0x12D591",
                  "correctIndex": "0x18C1"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard",
              "Hard": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of sentence?(H 7-9)",
                  "Option1": "Declarative",
                  "Option2":"Interrogative",
                  "Option3":"Imperative",
                  "Option4":"Narrative",
                  "correctIndex": "Imperative"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a synonym for 'diligent'?",
                  "Option1":"Lazy",
                  "Option2":"Hardworking",
                  "Option3":"Slow",
                  "Option4":"Unreliable",
                  "correctIndex": "Lazy"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the proper noun in the following sentence? 'The Eiffel Tower is in Paris.'",
                  "Option1": "The",
                  "Option2": "Eiffel",
                  "Option3": "Tower",
                  "Option4": "Paris",
                  "correctIndex": "The"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the past tense of the verb 'run'?",
                  "Option1": "Runned",
                  "Option2": "Runneded",
                  "Option3": "Ran",
                  "Option4": "Runneded",
                  "correctIndex": "Ran"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a compound word?",
                  "Option1": "Bird",
                  "Option2": "House",
                  "Option3": "Basketball",
                  "Option4": "Table",
                  "correctIndex": "House"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct verb tense to use in the following sentence? 'I _____ my homework yesterday.'",
                  "Option1": "Do",
                  "Option2": "Did",
                  "Option3": "Done",
                  "Option4": "Doing",
                  "correctIndex": "Do"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]

            }
          ]
        },
        {  "English": "10-12",
          "10-12" :  [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic",
              "Basic": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following words means 'a fear of long words (B 10-12)'?",
                  "Option1": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia",
                  "Option2":"Sesquipedalophobia",
                  "Option3":"Phobophobia",
                  "Option4":"Logophobia",
                  "correctIndex": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct possessive form of the name 'Jones'?",
                  "Option1":"Jones",
                  "Option2":"Jone's",
                  "Option3":"Jones's",
                  "Option4":"Joneses",
                  "correctIndex": "Jones's"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a rhetorical device?",
                  "Option1": "Metaphor",
                  "Option2": "Alliteration",
                  "Option3": "Onomatopoeia",
                  "Option4": "Synonym",
                  "correctIndex": "Synonym"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the difference between 'few' and 'a few'?",
                  "Option1": "There is no difference",
                  "Option2": "'Few' means none, while 'a few' means some",
                  "Option3": "'Few' means some, while 'a few' means many",
                  "Option4": "'Few' is an adverb, while 'a few' is a pronoun",
                  "correctIndex": "There is no difference"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'goose'?",
                  "Option1": "Gooses",
                  "Option2": "Goosen",
                  "Option3": "Geese",
                  "Option4": "Gooseses",
                  "correctIndex": "Geese"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a correlative conjunction?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Neither...nor",
                  "correctIndex": "Neither...nor"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of an indirect object?",
                  "Option1": "He gave her a book.",
                  "Option2": "She ran quickly to the store.",
                  "Option3": "The sun set behind the mountains",
                  "Option4": "I ate pizza for dinner.",
                  "correctIndex": "He gave her a book."
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium",
              "Medium" : [
                {
                  "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly? (M 10-12)",
                  "Option1": "Apis",
                  "Option2":"Coleoptera",
                  "Option3":"Formicidae",
                  "Option4":"Rhopalocera",
                  "correctIndex": "Formicidae"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
                  "Option1":"1,233 K",
                  "Option2":"5,778 K",
                  "Option3":"12,130 K",
                  "Option4":"101,300 K",
                  "correctIndex": "1,233 K"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Who are the actors in The Internship?",
                  "Option1": "Ben Stiller, Jonah Hill",
                  "Option2": "Courteney Cox, Matt LeBlanc",
                  "Option3": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons",
                  "Option4": "Vince Vaughn, Owen Wilson",
                  "correctIndex": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the capital of Spain?",
                  "Option1": "Berlin",
                  "Option2": "Buenos Aires",
                  "Option3": "Madrid",
                  "Option4": "San Juan",
                  "correctIndex": "Buenos Aires"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 70 degrees Fahrenheit in Celsius?",
                  "Option1": "18.8889",
                  "Option2": "20",
                  "Option3": "21.1111",
                  "Option4": "158",
                  "correctIndex": "20"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When was Mahatma Gandhi born?",
                  "Option1": "October 2, 1869",
                  "Option2": "December 15, 1872",
                  "Option3": "July 18, 1918",
                  "Option4": "January 15, 1929",
                  "correctIndex": "October 2, 1869"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How far is the moon from Earth?",
                  "Option1": "7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
                  "Option2": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
                  "Option3": "238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
                  "Option4": "35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)",
                  "correctIndex": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 65 times 52?",
                  "Option1": "117",
                  "Option2": "3120",
                  "Option3": "3380",
                  "Option4": "3520",
                  "correctIndex": "3120"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How tall is Mount Everest?",
                  "Option1": "6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
                  "Option2": "7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
                  "Option3": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
                  "Option4": "29,029 ft (8,847 m)",
                  "correctIndex": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When did The Avengers come out?",
                  "Option1": "May 2, 2008",
                  "Option2": "May 4, 2012",
                  "Option3": "May 3, 2013",
                  "Option4": "April 4, 2014",
                  "correctIndex": "May 2, 2008"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
                  "Option1": "0x18C1",
                  "Option2": "0xBEEF",
                  "Option3": "0xDEAD",
                  "Option4": "0x12D591",
                  "correctIndex": "0x18C1"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard",
              "Hard": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of sentence?(H 10-12)",
                  "Option1": "Declarative",
                  "Option2":"Interrogative",
                  "Option3":"Imperative",
                  "Option4":"Narrative",
                  "correctIndex": "Imperative"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a synonym for 'diligent'?",
                  "Option1":"Lazy",
                  "Option2":"Hardworking",
                  "Option3":"Slow",
                  "Option4":"Unreliable",
                  "correctIndex": "Lazy"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the proper noun in the following sentence? 'The Eiffel Tower is in Paris.'",
                  "Option1": "The",
                  "Option2": "Eiffel",
                  "Option3": "Tower",
                  "Option4": "Paris",
                  "correctIndex": "The"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the past tense of the verb 'run'?",
                  "Option1": "Runned",
                  "Option2": "Runneded",
                  "Option3": "Ran",
                  "Option4": "Runneded",
                  "correctIndex": "Ran"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a compound word?",
                  "Option1": "Bird",
                  "Option2": "House",
                  "Option3": "Basketball",
                  "Option4": "Table",
                  "correctIndex": "House"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct verb tense to use in the following sentence? 'I _____ my homework yesterday.'",
                  "Option1": "Do",
                  "Option2": "Did",
                  "Option3": "Done",
                  "Option4": "Doing",
                  "correctIndex": "Do"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]

            }
          ]
        },
        { "English": "12+ / B tech",
          "12+ / B tech" :  [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic",
              "Basic": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following words means 'a fear of long words (12+ / B tech)'?",
                  "Option1": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia",
                  "Option2":"Sesquipedalophobia",
                  "Option3":"Phobophobia",
                  "Option4":"Logophobia",
                  "correctIndex": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct possessive form of the name 'Jones'?",
                  "Option1":"Jones",
                  "Option2":"Jone's",
                  "Option3":"Jones's",
                  "Option4":"Joneses",
                  "correctIndex": "Jones's"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a rhetorical device?",
                  "Option1": "Metaphor",
                  "Option2": "Alliteration",
                  "Option3": "Onomatopoeia",
                  "Option4": "Synonym",
                  "correctIndex": "Synonym"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the difference between 'few' and 'a few'?",
                  "Option1": "There is no difference",
                  "Option2": "'Few' means none, while 'a few' means some",
                  "Option3": "'Few' means some, while 'a few' means many",
                  "Option4": "'Few' is an adverb, while 'a few' is a pronoun",
                  "correctIndex": "There is no difference"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'goose'?",
                  "Option1": "Gooses",
                  "Option2": "Goosen",
                  "Option3": "Geese",
                  "Option4": "Gooseses",
                  "correctIndex": "Geese"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a correlative conjunction?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Neither...nor",
                  "correctIndex": "Neither...nor"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of an indirect object?",
                  "Option1": "He gave her a book.",
                  "Option2": "She ran quickly to the store.",
                  "Option3": "The sun set behind the mountains",
                  "Option4": "I ate pizza for dinner.",
                  "correctIndex": "He gave her a book."
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium",
              "Medium" : [
                {
                  "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly? (12+ / B tech)",
                  "Option1": "Apis",
                  "Option2":"Coleoptera",
                  "Option3":"Formicidae",
                  "Option4":"Rhopalocera",
                  "correctIndex": "Formicidae"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
                  "Option1":"1,233 K",
                  "Option2":"5,778 K",
                  "Option3":"12,130 K",
                  "Option4":"101,300 K",
                  "correctIndex": "1,233 K"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Who are the actors in The Internship?",
                  "Option1": "Ben Stiller, Jonah Hill",
                  "Option2": "Courteney Cox, Matt LeBlanc",
                  "Option3": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons",
                  "Option4": "Vince Vaughn, Owen Wilson",
                  "correctIndex": "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the capital of Spain?",
                  "Option1": "Berlin",
                  "Option2": "Buenos Aires",
                  "Option3": "Madrid",
                  "Option4": "San Juan",
                  "correctIndex": "Buenos Aires"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 70 degrees Fahrenheit in Celsius?",
                  "Option1": "18.8889",
                  "Option2": "20",
                  "Option3": "21.1111",
                  "Option4": "158",
                  "correctIndex": "20"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When was Mahatma Gandhi born?",
                  "Option1": "October 2, 1869",
                  "Option2": "December 15, 1872",
                  "Option3": "July 18, 1918",
                  "Option4": "January 15, 1929",
                  "correctIndex": "October 2, 1869"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How far is the moon from Earth?",
                  "Option1": "7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
                  "Option2": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
                  "Option3": "238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
                  "Option4": "35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)",
                  "correctIndex": "86,881 miles (139,822 km)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 65 times 52?",
                  "Option1": "117",
                  "Option2": "3120",
                  "Option3": "3380",
                  "Option4": "3520",
                  "correctIndex": "3120"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How tall is Mount Everest?",
                  "Option1": "6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
                  "Option2": "7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
                  "Option3": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
                  "Option4": "29,029 ft (8,847 m)",
                  "correctIndex": "19,341 ft (5,895 m)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When did The Avengers come out?",
                  "Option1": "May 2, 2008",
                  "Option2": "May 4, 2012",
                  "Option3": "May 3, 2013",
                  "Option4": "April 4, 2014",
                  "correctIndex": "May 2, 2008"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
                  "Option1": "0x18C1",
                  "Option2": "0xBEEF",
                  "Option3": "0xDEAD",
                  "Option4": "0x12D591",
                  "correctIndex": "0x18C1"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard",
              "Hard": [
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of sentence?(12+ / B tech)",
                  "Option1": "Declarative",
                  "Option2":"Interrogative",
                  "Option3":"Imperative",
                  "Option4":"Narrative",
                  "correctIndex": "Imperative"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a synonym for 'diligent'?",
                  "Option1":"Lazy",
                  "Option2":"Hardworking",
                  "Option3":"Slow",
                  "Option4":"Unreliable",
                  "correctIndex": "Lazy"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the proper noun in the following sentence? 'The Eiffel Tower is in Paris.'",
                  "Option1": "The",
                  "Option2": "Eiffel",
                  "Option3": "Tower",
                  "Option4": "Paris",
                  "correctIndex": "The"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the past tense of the verb 'run'?",
                  "Option1": "Runned",
                  "Option2": "Runneded",
                  "Option3": "Ran",
                  "Option4": "Runneded",
                  "correctIndex": "Ran"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
                  "Option1": "Black, Red",
                  "Option2": "Blue, Orange",
                  "Option3": "White, Burnt Orange",
                  "Option4": "White, Old gold, Gold",
                  "correctIndex": "Blue, Orange"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a compound word?",
                  "Option1": "Bird",
                  "Option2": "House",
                  "Option3": "Basketball",
                  "Option4": "Table",
                  "correctIndex": "House"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the correct verb tense to use in the following sentence? 'I _____ my homework yesterday.'",
                  "Option1": "Do",
                  "Option2": "Did",
                  "Option3": "Done",
                  "Option4": "Doing",
                  "correctIndex": "Do"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the plural form of the word 'child'?",
                  "Option1": "Childs",
                  "Option2": "Childen",
                  "Option3": "Children",
                  "Option4": "Childies",
                  "correctIndex": "Children"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is a preposition?",
                  "Option1": "And",
                  "Option2": "But",
                  "Option3": "Or",
                  "Option4": "Under",
                  "correctIndex": "Or"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the adverb in the following sentence? 'She sings beautifully.'",
                  "Option1": "She",
                  "Option2": "Sings",
                  "Option3": "Beautifully",
                  "Option4": "Sings beautifully",
                  "correctIndex": "Sings"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simile?",
                  "Option1": "The sun is a ball of fire.",
                  "Option2": "She runs as fast as a cheetah.",
                  "Option3": "The tree branches swayed in the wind.",
                  "Option4": "The cat meowed loudly.",
                  "correctIndex": "The sun is a ball of fire."
                }
              ]

            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Subject": "Hindi",
      "Hindi": [
        {
          "Hindi": "1-3",
          "1-3" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Hindi": "4-6",
          "4-6" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        { "Hindi": "7-9",
          "7-9" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Hindi": "10-12",
          "10-12" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        { "Hindi": "12+ / B tech",
          "12+ / B tech" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Subject": "Math",
      "Math": [
        {
          "Math": "1-3",
          "1-3" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Math": "4-6",
          "4-6" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        { "Math": "7-9",
          "7-9" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Math": "10-12",
          "10-12" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "Math": "12+ / B tech",
          "12+ / B tech" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Subject": "Social Science",
      "Social Science": [
        {
          "Social Science": "1-3",
          "1-3" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Social Science": "4-6",
          "4-6" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        { "Social Science": "7-9",
          "7-9" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Social Science": "10-12",
          "10-12" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "Social Science": "12+ / B tech",
          "12+ / B tech" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]


    },
    {
      "Subject": "Science",
      "Science": [
        {
          "Science": "1-3",
          "1-3" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Science": "4-6",
          "4-6" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        { "Science": "7-9",
          "7-9" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {  "Science": "10-12",
          "10-12" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "Science": "12+ / B tech",
          "12+ / B tech" : [
            {
              "Diff": "Basic"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Medium"
            },
            {
              "Diff": "Hard"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "Ranges": [
    {
      "Range": "1-3"
    },
    {
     "Range": "4-6"
    },
    {
      "Range": "7-9"
    },
    {
      "Range": "10-12"
    },
    {
      "Range": "12+ / B tech"
    }
  ],
  "Difficulty" : [
    {
      "Difficult": "Basic"
    },
    {
      "Difficult": "Medium"
    },
    {
      "Difficult": "Hard"
    }
  ]
}

